rodp.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement | TNeCampus.info

The privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit Tennessee Board of Regents (TBR) websites are important to us. No personal information is collected at this site unless it is provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an activity that asks for the information. The following paragraphs disclose the information gathering and usage practices for the web site.

## **Collection of Information**

The TBR only collects the personally identifiable information that is necessary to provide the information or services requested by an individual[LPS1] . "Personal information" refers to any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. This is the same information that an individual might provide when visiting a government office and includes such items as an individual's name, address, or phone number.  The TBR uses the collected information to respond appropriately to requests.  This may be to respond directly to you or to improve the website.  E-mail or other information requests sent to the TBR website may be maintained or forwarded to the appropriate agencies in order to respond to the request. Survey information is used for the purpose designated in the survey.

The TBR also collects statistical information that helps us understand how people are using the website so we can continually improve our services. The information collected is not associated with any specific individual and no attempt is made to profile individuals who browse the website.  This information includes, but is not limited to:

  * Device-specific information (hardware, operating system, language and browser type)
  * Log information (IP address, search queries and referral URL)
  * Local storage, cookies and anonymous identifiers to collect and store information locally on your device

## **Retention of Information**

Records needed to support TBR program functions are retained, managed, and accessible in record keeping or filing systems in accordance with established records disposition authorizations approved by the State of Tennessee’s Public Records Commission. Records transmitted to this site will be identified, managed, protected, and retained as long as they are needed to meet historical, administrative, fiscal, or legal requirements.

## **Public Disclosure**

Regardless of whether information is provided to the TBR by personal visit, mail, or website, it becomes public record and is open to public inspection unless protected by State or Federal law. Public records are subject to the rules and requirements located in Tennessee Code Annotated Title 10 Chapter 7. A public record is defined as follows:

"Public record(s)" or "state record(s)" means all documents, papers, letters, maps, books, photographs, microfilms, electronic data processing files and output, films, sound recordings or other material, regardless of physical form or characteristics made or received pursuant to law or ordinance or in connection with the transaction of official business by any governmental agency. (T.C.A. 10-7-301 (6))

Based on the definition of public records, be aware that any information collected at this site could be made available to the public. Requests for public records will be examined for compliance with public record laws.

## **Website Security**

The TBR is committed to the security of the information that is either available from or collected by this website. The TBR has taken multiple steps to safeguard the integrity of its telecommunications and computing infrastructure, including but not limited to, authentication, monitoring, auditing, encryption (SSL) and various physical safeguards.

## **Links to Other Sites**

This website has links to many other websites. These include links to websites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. The TBR is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites and suggests you review their privacy statements.

## **FERPA Rights to Privacy**

The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) (20 U.S.C. § 1232g; 34 CFR Part 99) is a Federal law that protects the privacy of student education records. The law applies to all schools that receive funds under an applicable program of the U.S. Department of Education.

FERPA gives parents certain rights with respect to their children's education records. These rights transfer to the student when he or she reaches the age of 18 or attends a school beyond the high school level. Students to whom the rights have transferred are "eligible students."

For more information on FERPA, please see the [Department of Education website](http://www2.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html?src=ft).

## **Application**

Our Privacy Statement applies to all websites and services offered by the TBR, its units and their activities, its initiatives, its programs and collaborations, and work being done on behalf of the TBR by its contractors and partners, but exclude services that have separate privacy statements.  The TBR Privacy Statement does not apply to its member institutions.

## **Changes**

The TBR Privacy Statement may be changed at any time without notice or consent.   All changes will be posted on the website.

## **Contact Information**

Tennessee Board of Regents  
TN eCampus
